#### Contact

L.Clint91@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/clint-lee (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

React and Firebase for rich interactive application development.

HTML5, CSS3 and responsive design

JavaScript fundamentals, jQuery and using REST APIs

# Clint Lee

Front-End Web Developer

Toronto, Canada Area

### Summary

Hello, my name is Clint Lee and I'm a bilingual front-end web developer based in Toronto. I have a strong passion for learning and writing intuitive, functional, clean codes providing engaging applications and websites that are creatively designed and accessible. I look forward to being part of supportive and innovative team that wants to create exceptional UX on the internet for all end-users.

Growing up in Seoul, South Korea, I had many opportunities to experience the newest technologies and fell in love with the task of figuring out how they work. For as long as I can remember I have been interested in the limitless possibilities of Information Technology and became fascinated with the world of programming.

Code meets music, that is who I am. I love creating music and singing along with my acoustic guitar. When I'm not coding, you will find me DJing, making music on the computer or with my guitar, or image training snowboard tricks for the winter season (Canadian winter rocks!).

## Experience

HackerYou College of Technology Student September 2017 - Present Toronto, Canada Area

Maple Woods Cinema
Video Editor / Camera Operator
March 2017 - September 2017 (7 months)
Oshawa

- Recorded and edited Youtube contents for businesses(Chef's Plate) and private weddings with Adobe Premiere and After Effects

Page 1 of 2

- Media management, asset organization, and file delivery for both online and offline

## Education

HackerYou College of Technology Web Development · (2018 - 2018)

HackerYou College of Technology Web Development · (2018 - 2018)

HackerYou College of Technology Web Development · (2017 - 2017)

Loyalist College
Television and New Media Production · (2015 - 2017)